Bare Bodkin Theatre Company Records UA230
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, 2015 -- 2017; UA230.000286; 3.42 Gigabytes; 54 Digital Object(s) 54 digital objects comprising 917 files.
  - 2015 -- 2016 academic year records, UA230.000287; 1.58 Gigabytes; 14 Digital Object(s) 14 digital objects comprising 196 files.
    - Artists in residence, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000288; 67.3 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Bodkin Major, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000289; 73.58 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 63 files.
    - General Interest Meeting-Fairs material, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000290; 44.83 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
    - Meeting minutes, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000291; 857.01 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 29 files.
    - Minors, theses, co-sponsorships, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000292; 1.81 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - Play by Play, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000293; 6.77 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 41 files.
    - Salons, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000294; 707.14 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Schwasty Fall, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000295; 84.97 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Schwasty Spring, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000296; 181.41 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Treasurer things, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000297; 9.67 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 file.
    - Website, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000298; 441.33 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Workshops, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000299; 350.3 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
    - Loose files, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.000300; 194 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - 2016 -- 2017 academic year records, UA230.000301; 1.84 Gigabytes; 39 Digital Object(s) 39 digital objects comprising 721 files.
    This series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2016 and 2017. These records include photographs and planning documents related to workshops, productions, and other Bare Bodkin events; artists in residence documents; Board meeting minutes; budgets; constitutional changes; and general interest meeting material. The predominant file formats in this series include the following, in order of prevalence: JPEG, Word documents, and MPEG.
    - Artists in residence, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000302; 110.25 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Board meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000303; 1.21 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 22 files.
    - Constitutional changes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000304; 175.69 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Co-sponsorship proposals, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000305; 16.53 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Four year plan, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000306; 11.29 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - General meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000307; 36.28 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - General Interest Meeting-Fairs materials, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000308; 15.09 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Bodkin Major, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000309; 1.13 Gigabytes; 27 Digital Object(s) 27 digital objects comprising 655 files.
      - Proposals, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000310; 368.55 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
      - The Clyt, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000311; 1.13 Gigabytes; 25 Digital Object(s) 25 digital objects comprising 650 files.
        - Design, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000312; 346.6 Megabytes; 9 Digital Object(s) 9 digital objects comprising 533 files.
          - Costumes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000313; 261.56 Megabytes; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects comprising 432 files.
            - Dan research, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000314; 24.69 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 204 files.
            - Final run rehearsal, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000315; 182.16 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 190 files.
            - Fitting photos, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000316; 30.46 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 31 files.
          - Lights, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000317; 11.16 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
          - Props, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000318; 11.35 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
          - Scenic, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000319; 3.86 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
          - Sound, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000320; 792 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 91 files.
        - Direction - dramaturgy, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000321; 775.26 Megabytes; 6 Digital Object(s) 6 digital objects comprising 33 files.
          - Auditions, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000322; 258.37 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
          - Design, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000323; 10.19 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
          - Fury movement videos, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000324; 748.98 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
          - Producing information, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000325; 15.76 Megabytes; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 digital objects comprising 18 files.
            - Lobby boxes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000326; 5.56 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 16 files.
        - Producing, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000327; 15.99 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
        - Script drafts, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000328; 2.41 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
        - Stage - production management, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000329; 34.52 Megabytes; 7 Digital Object(s) 7 digital objects comprising 75 files.
          - Auditions, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000330; 3.73 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 19 files.
          - Conflicts, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000331; 19.97 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
          - Line notes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000332; 52.42 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
          - Production staff minutes, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000333; 4.07 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
          - Rehearsal reports, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000334; 21.16 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 26 files.
          - Schedules, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000335; 5.07 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Play by Play, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000336; 688.07 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 18 files.
    - Schwasty Fall, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000337; 505.34 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Treasurer things, 2016 -- 2017; UA230.000338; 26.91 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Loose files, 2017; UA230.000339; 154 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.